hey everybody welcome back to the show
I'm so excited you know from time to
time we like to get an international
perspective on current
events mainly to confirm that we really
don't know anything about international
events so we're happy to welcome back to
the program our senior International
correspondent from South Africa Trevor
Noah is here
Trevor nice to see you thank you thank
you John thank you for being here yeah
obviously we're all still reeling from
the terrible events of January 7th so uh
oh right no that's uh the uh Charlie
ebdo Massacre Paris that was a oh well
well that that too but I was actually
talking about the bua and Doren buer
massacres in
Nigeria
yes Baga and Doran Baga is that are
those Nigerian satirical magazines I
don't uh no they they're towns John well
they they were towns B Haram destroyed
them and killed thousands of people yes
Boko Haram I've heard of them # Bring
Back Our Girls yes yeah yeah that's
right well hash they didn't uh in fact
since then boam has captured an area the
size of
Slovakia that's two
slovenians that's 9 million American
football field holy that's a lot of
area I did not realize you know what and
you're not the only one John not a
single head of state went to Nigeria
after the January attacks not even Obama
and he's African well well well he's a
africanamerican he was not born in
Africa born in Hawaii oh yeah right
yeah I got you I got you well look if it
makes you feel better Obama didn't go to
Paris either yeah but at least you could
have sent us James Taylor what Africa
doesn't get a
friend settle for Paul Simon oh okay but
only if he promises not to steal our
music # bring back our songs
look John in France 1.6 million people
marched for 12 cartoonists which is
great but by that math the whole world
should have been marching in Nigeria
like sometimes it just feels like Africa
is the Vagas of Islamic Terror what
happens in Africa stays in
Africa that was a tremendous
accent thank you well you know doesn't
it stay in in in Africa I mean does it
really affect us here I mean you think
that John but uh what about the
underwear bomber he was Nigerian oh
right and because of him you know nobody
is allowed to wear underwear on
airplanes
now I I think you
all better safe than sorry is what I
always saying point is this Charlie ebdo
was a direct attack on our Western
values of free speech and expression
right and boo Haram literally means
western education is
forbidden really you see John we're
fighting the same terrorism so next time
just include us in your marches Nigerian
school girls use pencils too so you
don't even have to change the
props you know we we we'd love to Trevor
honestly the states would love to but
our global war on terror calendar is so
full between the Isis and uh they're
trying to set up a caliphate yeah so is
Boo Haram they kidnap people they sell
them into slavery it's pretty Isis is
yeah they wear these costumes holy
that's Isis is that's like Isis could or
yeah Arab Spring collection in
fact they uh they even have the same
flag John they have the same flag that's
just lazy don't you see John Boh Haram
is black
Isis that sounds like the most awesome
Pam Greer movie
ever you know John boo Haram must feel
like Tyler Perry huge numbers but no
recognition
I look Trevor I get it but we're so busy
fighting you know what that's that's too
bad because if Bo aram's not stopped
they might take over Nigeria's oil
fields
and Nigeria's
what well oil Nigeria has the world's
10th biggest oil reserves 37 billion
barrels 37 billion
[Music]
barrels it's
funny actually as I think about it we do
have an opening
um right after I think we uh uh in
between Isis and Yemen I think we can
squeeze you in uh perhaps we can have
James Taylor over there right away all
we have to do is call and he'll be there
yes he
will you've got a
[Music]
friend justu too young to know that song
um but thank you thank you Trevor Trevor
know everybody we'll be right back
w